A Guide to the Virginia Room Vertical and Historic Landmark Files, Undated
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- HLF - Clifton - (1971-1975)
- HLF - Clifton - (1976-1980)
- HLF - Clifton - (1981-1985)
- HLF - Clifton - (1986-1990)
- HLF - Clifton - (1991 & later)
- HLF - Clifton - 7155 Pendleton
- HLF - Clifton - Beckwith House
- HLF - Clifton - Buckley Brothers Store
- HLF - Clifton - Clifton Hotel
- HLF - Clifton - Clifton Post Office
- HLF - Clifton - Clifton Store
- HLF - Clifton - Colchester Road
- HLF - Clifton - Gold Mining
- HLF - Clifton - Hetzel House
- HLF - Clifton - Historic District
- HLF - Clifton - Historic Homes
- HLF - Clifton - History
- HLF - Clifton - Kinchloe Property
- HLF - Clifton - Podonick Property
- HLF - Clifton - Power Substation
- VF - Climate
- HLF - Colchester Area - History
- HLF - Colchester Town Archaeological Site
- HLF - Coleman House
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1957-1963)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1964)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1965)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1966)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1967)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1968)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1969)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1970)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1971)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1972)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1973)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1974)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1975)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1976)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1977)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1978)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1979)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1980)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1981)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1982)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1983)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1984)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1985-1990)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - Administration
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - Dedication (1964)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - Housing/Dormitories
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - Law School
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - Library
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - Patriot Center
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - Police
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - Presidents House
- VF - Colleges & Universities - George Mason University - (1991- )
- VF - Colleges & Universities - Luther Rice College
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - Administration
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - WNVT TV
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - Woodbridge Campus
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - Manassas Campus
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - Alexandria Campus
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - Loudoun Campus
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1965)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1966)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1967)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1968)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1969)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1970)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1971)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1972)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1973)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1974)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1975)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1976-1980)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - No. Va. Community College - (1981-1985)
- VF - Colleges & Universities - University of Virginia - No. Va. Center
- VF - Colleges & Universities - Virginia Tech. - No. Va. Center
- HLF - Collier House - 6080 Leesburg Pike - Falls Church
- HLF - Collingwood
- HLF - Colvin Run Community Center
- HLF - Colvin Run Mill - (1 of 2)
- HLF - Colvin Run Mill - (2 of 2)
- HLF - Colvin Run Miller's House
- VF - Commission for Women
- VF - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education
- VF - Construction Industry
- HLF - Contemplation
- HLF - Cooke House - 00808 Swinks Mill Rd - McLean
- HLF - Cornwell Farm
- HLF - Cornwell House - 10010 Georgetown Place - Upper Potomac
- HLF - Cottage Grove
- HLF - Cottonwood Road neighborhood (McLean)
- HLF - Country Clubs
- VF - Courts - (General)
- VF - Courts - Circuit Court
- VF - Courts - General District Court
- VF - Courts - Judges
- VF - Courts - Justice of the Peace
- VF - Courts - Juvenile & Domestic Relations Court
- VF - Courts - Magistrates
- VF - Courts - Public Defenders
- VF - Courts - Small Claims
- VF - Crafts & Craftsmen - Silversmiths
- VF - Crime - Prevention - Neighborhood Watch
- VF - Crime - Prevention
- VF - Crime - Sexual Assault
- HLF - Crippen Barn (Reston, Va.).
- HLF - Cross Farmhouse (Chantilly, Va.).
- VF - Dams
- HLF - Dandru Farm (Vienna, Va.). - (Hunter House)
- HLF - Davis' General Store
- HLF - Davis House Ruins
- VF - Democratic Party
- VF - Descrimination
- VF - Descrimination - Women
- VF - Desegregation
- HLF - Deshayes House (Vienna, Va.).
- HLF - Dickey's Tavern
- VF - DILLON RULE
- HLF - Dixie Pig Barbeque Restaurant
- HLF - Doak House
- HLF - Dower House
- HLF - Downscrest - 1049 Crest Lane - McLean
- HLF - Dranesville Area - History
- HLF - Dranesville Area - History - Battle of Dranesville (Dec. 20, 1861)
- HLF - Dranesville Tavern
- HLF - Dranesville Tavern - (2 of 2) 11919 Leesburg Place - Upper Potomac
- HLF - Drovers Rest
- VF - Drugs
- VF - Drugs - Marijuana
- VF - Drugs - Treatment Programs
- HLF - Dulaney Barn/Harper House
- HLF - Dulin House
- HLF - Dunbarton
- HLF - Dunn Loring - Midgetville
- HLF - Dunn Loring - Poor Peoples Camp (1968)
- HLF - Dunn Loring Area - History
- HLF - Dunn Loring Historic District [Proposed]
- VF - Earthquakes
- HLF - Eastern Shore House - 10026 Colvin Run Road - Upper Potomac
- HLF - Egan House - - McLean
- HLF - Eglin House
- HLF - Eight Oaks (McLean, Va.).
- HLF - Elkins Station
- HLF - Elmdale Farm
- HLF - Elmwood
- HLF - Elwardstone
- VF - Employment
- VF - Energy
- VF - Energy - Energy Crisis (1973-74)
- VF - Energy - Energy Crisis (1977)
- VF - Energy - Energy Crisis (1979)
- HLF - Engleside Area
- HLF - Evans Farm Inn (McLean, Va.).
- HLF - Evergreen
- HLF - Exxon-Mobil Headquarters
- HLF - Fair Lakes Area
- HLF - Fair Oaks Area - Fairfax Corner
- HLF - Fair Oaks Area - Penderbrook
- HLF - Fair Oaks Mall & Vicinity
- FX - Fairfax
- FX - Fairfax - (1961-1965)
- FX - Fairfax - (1966-1970)
- FX - Fairfax - (1971-1975)
- FX - Fairfax - (1976-1980)
- FX - Fairfax - (1981-1985)
- FX - Fairfax - (1986-1990)
- FX - Fairfax - (1991-1995)
- FX - Fairfax - (1996-2000)
- FX - Fairfax - (2001-2005)
- FX - Fairfax - (2006-2010)
- FX - Fairfax - (2011-)
- FX - Fairfax - American Legion Post No.177
- FX - Fairfax - Anderson Monument
- FX - Fairfax - Barbour House
- FX - Fairfax - Blenheim
- FX - Fairfax - Blincoe House
- FX - Fairfax - Britt House
- FX - Fairfax - Brouwer House
- FX - Fairfax - Churches - (General)
- FX - Fairfax - Churches - Fairfax United Methodist Church
- FX - Fairfax - Churches - St. Leo's Catholic Church
- FX - Fairfax - Churches - Truro Episcopal Church & Rectory
- FX - Fairfax - Churches - Christian Science
- FX - Fairfax - Churches - Fairfax Baptist Church
- FX - Fairfax - Churches - Fairfax Christian
- FX - Fairfax - Churches - Fairfax Presbyterian
- FX - Fairfax - Churches - Mt. Calvary Baptist Church
- FX - Fairfax - City Hall
- HLF - Fairfax - Clark House - 9999 Main Street
- FX - Fairfax - Cobbdale Subdivision
- FX - Fairfax - Community Centers
- FX - Fairfax - Constantine
- FX - Fairfax - Coomb Cottage
- FX - Fairfax - Courthouse Plaza
- FX - Fairfax - Curran House
- FX - Fairfax - Dandridge House
- HLF - Fairfax - Donohoe House
- FX - Fairfax - Downtown Redevelopment - (2000- )
- FX - Fairfax - Draper House
- FX - Fairfax - Earp's Ordinary - (See: Ratcliffe/Allison House)
- FX - Fairfax - Fairfax Hardware
- FX - Fairfax - Fairfax Hay and Grain
- FX - Fairfax - Fairfax Herald Building
- FX - Fairfax - Fairview
- FX - Fairfax - Five Chimneys - (Farr Homeplace) includes Ballynahown
- FX - Fairfax - Ford Building
- FX - Fairfax - Great Oaks Subdivision
- FX - Fairfax - High Offley
- FX - Fairfax - Historic Fairfax City, Inc.
- FX - Fairfax - Historic Homes
- FX - Fairfax - Historic Markers
- FX - Fairfax - History - (Pre-1961)
- FX - Fairfax - History - Civil War
- FX - Fairfax - History - Historic District
- FX - Fairfax - History - Historical Trail
- FX - Fairfax - History - Observances
- FX - Fairfax - Hope Farm
- FX - Fairfax - Hurricane David
- FX - Fairfax - Kamp Washington
- FX - Fairfax - Krasnow/Mackall Property
- FX - Fairfax - Layton Hall
- FX - Fairfax - Little River Hills
- FX - Fairfax - Moore/McCandlish House
- FX - Fairfax - Mosby Woods Subdivision
- FX - Fairfax - Mount Vinyard (Fairfax, Va.).
- HLF - Fairfax - Mount Vinyard (Fairfax, Va.).
- FX - Fairfax - Museum and Visitors' Center
- FX - Fairfax - National Bank of Fairfax
- FX - Fairfax - Officials
- FX - Fairfax - Old Town Hall - (Willard Hall)
- FX - Fairfax - Old Town Square
- FX - Fairfax - Oliver House - Joshua C. Gunnell House
- FX - Fairfax - Parks & Recreation
- FX - Fairfax - Post Office
- FX - Fairfax - Ralston's Store
- FX - Fairfax - Ratcliffe/Allison House
- FX - Fairfax - Restaurants
- FX - Fairfax - Roads
- FX - Fairfax - Rustfield
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Belle Willard E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Daniels Run E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Fairfax E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Green Acres E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Jermantown E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - John C. Wood E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Layton Hall E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Mosby Woods E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Providence E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Westmore E.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Fairfax H.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - (Pre-1961)
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Lanier I.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Officials
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Parochial
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Private
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - (1961-1969)
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - (1970-1979)
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - (1980-1989)
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - (1990-1999)
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - (2000- )
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Fairfax Colored School [Rosenwald]
- FX - Fairfax - Schools - Paul VI H.S.
- FX - Fairfax - Seals & Symbols
- FX - Fairfax - Sewers
- FX - Fairfax - Sherwood House
- FX - Fairfax - Shurman House - (Krasnow Property)
- FX - Fairfax - Tank Farm
- FX - Fairfax - Tastee 29 Diner
- FX - Fairfax - Tornado (1973)
- FX - Fairfax - Transportation - Metrorail
- FX - Fairfax - Transportation - Buses - Fairfax City Express
- FX - Fairfax - Transportation - Buses - CUE Bus
- FX - Fairfax - Transportation - Buses - Dial-a-Ride
- FX - Fairfax - Transportation
- HLF - Fairfax - Vincent's Octagon - Fuddruckers
- FX - Fairfax - Water Supply
- FX - Fairfax - Westmore Subdivision
- FX - Fairfax - Willcoxon Tavern
- HLF - Fairfax Arms Tavern (Colchester, Va.).
- VF - Fairfax Bar Association
- VF - Fairfax Co. - Parks - Water Mine Family Swimmin' Hole
- VF - Fairfax Community Action Program
- HLF - Fairfax County - Gazetteers
- HLF - Fairfax County - History
- HLF - Fairfax County - History
- HLF - Fairfax County - History
- HLF - Fairfax County - History
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Civil War
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Maryland Gazette Abstracts
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Militia
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Northern Neck Grants
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Public Utilities
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Revolutionary War
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Oral Histories
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Revolutionary War
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Bicentennial
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - City Status 1961
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - City Status 1962-1965
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - City Status 1965-1969
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Civil War
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Civil War Lincoln at Crossroads
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Civil War Sesquicentennial
- HLF - Fairfax County - History - Civil War Soldiers' Correspondence
- HLF - Fairfax County - Trivia
- VF - Fairfax County Council on the Arts
- HLF - Fairfax County Courthouse (Fairfax, Va.). - (1 of 3)
- HLF - Fairfax County Courthouse (Fairfax, Va.). - (2 of 3)
- HLF - Fairfax County Courthouse (Fairfax, Va.). - (3 of 3)
- HLF - Fairfax County Courthouse (Fairfax, Va.). - 1742 Site
- HLF - Fairfax County Courthouse (Fairfax, Va.). - Monuments
- HLF - Fairfax County Courthouse (Fairfax, Va.). - Portraits
- VF - Fairfax County Cultural Association
- VF - Fairfax County Economic Development Authority
- VF - Fairfax County Environmental Qual. Adv. Council
- VF - Fairfax County Fair
- VF - Fairfax County Federation of Civic Associations
- HLF - Fairfax County Government Center - (1 of 2)
- HLF - Fairfax County Government Center - (2 of 2)
- HLF - Fairfax County Historic Landmark
- HLF - Fairfax County Historic Sites
- VF - Fairfax County Human Rights Commission
- HLF - Fairfax County Jail (Fairfax, Va.).
- HLF - Fairfax County Judicial Center
- HLF - Fairfax County Militia
- HLF - Fairfax County Museum
- VF - Fairfax County Planning Commission
- HLF - Fairfax County Records
- HLF - Fairfax County Records - Archives
- HLF - Fairfax County Records - Circuit Court Indexing Project
- HLF - Fairfax County Records - Washington Family Wills
- VF - Fairfax County Redevelopment Housing Authority
- VF - Fairfax County Taxpayers Alliance
- VF - Fairfax County Water Authority
- HLF - Fairfax Family Landholdings
- HLF - Fairfax Hunt(Reston, Va.).
- HLF - Fairfax Resolves
- HLF - Fairfax Station (Fairfax station, Va.).
- HLF - Fairfax Stone
- VF - Fairfax Symphony
- HLF - Fairfax Villa Park
- VF - Fairfax-Falls Church Community Services Board
- HLF - Fairhaven Subdivision
- HLF - Fairlee Subdivision (Fairfax, Va.).
- HLF - Falls Church - Balloon Houses (1941)
- HLF - Falls Church - Cherry Hill Farm
- HLF - Falls Church - Church Hill
- HLF - Falls Church - Churches
- HLF - Falls Church - Churches - Falls Church Episcopal Church
- HLF - Falls Church - Churches - St. James Catholic Church
- HLF - Falls Church - Cloverdale
- HLF - Falls Church - Dye-Burke House - (6718 Montour Dr.)
- HLF - Falls Church - Ellen McConvey House - (2119 Great Falls St.)
- HLF - Falls Church - Falls Church Railroad Station
- HLF - Falls Church - Hanging Tree
- HLF - Falls Church - History - (1 of 2)
- HLF - Falls Church - History - (2 of 2)
- HLF - Farmington (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Faulkner House
- HLF - Ferry Landing
- HLF - Fincastle Express (June 26, 1863)
- VF - Fire & Rescue - (1970-1975)
- VF - Fire & Rescue - (1976-1977)
- VF - Fire & Rescue - (1978-1979)
- VF - Fire & Rescue - (1980-1989)
- VF - Fire & Rescue - (1990-1999)
- VF - Fire & Rescue - (Pre-1970)
- VF - Fire & Rescue - 911 Service
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Annandale VFD - Stations 8 & 23
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Baileys Crossroads VFD - Station 10
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Burke VFD - Station 14
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Centreville VFD - Station 17
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Chantilly VFD - Station 15
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Clifton VFD - Station 16
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Fox Mill - Station 31
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Franconia VFD - Station 5
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Greater Springfield VFD - Stations 22 & 27
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Gunston - Station 20
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Herndon VFD - Station 4
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Jefferson VFD - Station 18
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - McLean VFD - Station 1
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Mount Vernon VFD - Station 9
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Navy-Vale VFD (Fair Oaks) - Station 21
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Penn-Daw VFD - Station 11
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Seven Corners - Station 28
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Vienna VFD - Station 2
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Woodlawn - Station 24
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Dunn Loring - Station 13
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Edall Road - Station 26
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Great Falls - Station 12
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - North Point - Station 39
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Reston - Station 25
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Companies - Fairfax VFD - Station 33
- VF - Fire & Rescue - Disaster Planning
- VF - Fish & Fishing
- HLF - Fitzgerald House - Georgetown Pike - Dranesville
- HLF - Fitzhugh Plantation (Falls Church, Va.). - (Mordecai Fitzhugh House)
- VF - Floods
- HLF - Floris - Keyes House (Herndon, Va.).
- HLF - Floris Area - History - Frying Pan Area
- HLF - Follin House
- HLF - Forestville Area - History
- HLF - Fort Belvoir (Fort Belvoir, Va.).
- HLF - Fort Belvoir Area - History
- HLF - Fort Belvoir Railroad Bridge - Route 1
- HLF - Fort Hunt (Civil War)
- HLF - Fort Lyon (Civil War)
- HLF - Fort Marcy (Civil War)
- HLF - Fort Willard Circle
- HLF - Four Stairs (Great Falls, Va.).
- HLF - Fox's Mill
- HLF - Franconia - Manchester Lakes
- HLF - Franconia - New Franconia
- HLF - Franconia Area - History
- HLF - Franklin Farm
- HLF - Franklin Park Subdivision
- HLF - Freedom Hill Fort (Vienna, Va.).
- HLF - Frozen Dairy Bar (Falls Church, Va.).
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - ANNANDALE
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - BRADDOCK
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - DRANESVILLE
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - LEE
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - MOUNT VERNON
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - SULLY
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - HUNTER MILL
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - PROVIDENCE
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - MASON
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - SPRINGFIELD
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - CENTREVILLE
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Districts - FALLS CHURCH
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Ethics/Disclosure
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Campaign Regulation
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Salaries & Expenses
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Zoning Scandal - (1966)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Zoning Scandal - (1967)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Board of Supervisors - Zoning Scandal - (1968-1969)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Boundaries
- VF - Fx. Co. - Charter
- VF - Fx. Co. - Clubs & Organizations
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1966)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1967)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1968)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1969)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (Pre-1966)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - Officials
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - Computers
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - Consumer Affairs
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1970)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1971)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1972)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1973)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1974)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1975)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1976)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1977)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1978)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1979)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - (1980 & later)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - Print Shop
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - Descrimination
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - Boards, Commissions, Etc…
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - Bond Sales
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - Environmental Services
- VF - Fx. Co. - Government - Employees
- VF - Fx. Co. - Health Department
- VF - Fx. Co. - Housing
- VF - Fx. Co. - Human Services
- VF - Fx. Co. - Mental Health
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - (1961-1970)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - (1971-1980)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Blue Laws
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Bottles (Deposits)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Dancing
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Firearms
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Loitering
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Massage Parlors
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Motor Bikes
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Noise
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Pinball Machines
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Signs
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Smoking
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Solicitors
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Swimming Pools
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Obscenity - (1975-1976)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Obscenity - (1977)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Obscenity - (1978-1980)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Obscenity - (1981-1990)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Obscenity - Croatan Books, Inc.
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Obscenity - Crossroads Books
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Obscenity - Educational Books, Inc.
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Service Stations
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Street Numbers
- VF - Fx. Co. - Ordinances - Revitalization Tax Abatement
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1950-1959)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1960-1963)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1964)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1965)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1966)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1967)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1968)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1969)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1970)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1971)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1972)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1973)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1974)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1975)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1976)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1977)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1978)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1979)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1980)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1981)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1982)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1983)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1984)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1985)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1986)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1987)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1988)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1989)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1990)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - (1991-1995)
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Annandale
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Baileys
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Bull Run
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Fairfax
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Jefferson
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Lincolnia
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Lower Potomac
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - McLean
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Mount Vernon
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Pohick
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Rose Hill
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Springfield